A Guide to the Thomas N. Downing Papers, 1947-1977
Library of Virginia
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 118)
  - General Files [and General Legislation].
    - Virginia Council on Health and Medical Care
    - Virginia Military Institute [VMI]
    - Virginia Military Institute Fund
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute [VPI]
    - Virginia State Poultry Federation, Inc.
    - Virginia Waterman's Association
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 119)
  - General Files [and General Legislation].
    - Warwick
    - Washapregue
    - Pokey the Whale
    - White House Tours and General White House Stuff [sic]
    - College of William and Mary
    - Williamsburg
    - W--General
    - York County
    - Yorktown Job Corps
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 120)
  - General Files [and General Legislation].
    - Zucker, Sylvia--Peninsula Association for Retarded Children [PARC] (3 folders)
    - Zucker, Sylvia--Grant Application
    - X-Z--General
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 121)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, January-December 1965 (12 folders)
    - Invitations Regretted, January-February 1965 (2 folders)
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 122)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Regretted, March-October 1965 (8 folders)
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 123)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Declined, November-December 1965 (2 folders)
    - Invitations extended [1965]
    - Daybook and Memorandum Booklet, 1965
    - Invitations Accepted, January-July 1966 (7 folders)
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 124)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, August-December 1966 (5 folders)
    - Acceptances, 1965-1966
    - Invitations Declined, January-May 1966 (5 folders)
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 125)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Declined, June-December 1966 (7 folders)
    - Invitations Extended, 1966
    - Daybook and Memorandum Booklet, 1966
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 126)
  - Legislation Enacted.
    - Contiguous Fisheries Zone Beyond Territorial Sea of U.S.
    - Fish Protein Concentrate (H.R. 16619)
  - Legislation Not Enacted, 1st Session.
    - Holland Memorial (2 folders)
    - Jones, John Paul
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries.
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 127)
  - Legislation Not Enacted, 2nd Session.
    - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission (H.J. Res. 967)
    - Closing of Public Health Service Hospitals
    - Delmarva Hydrology Bill (H.R. 13924)
    - Crab Packers Wage Amendment (H.R. 13712).
      Note: See also Boxes 49-51 and 96.
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries.
    - Representative Government Commission, 24 February 1966
    - Seafood Canners--Fair Labor Standards Act.
      Note: See also boxes 49-51 and 96.
    - Sherman, Susanne (H.R. 17411)
  - Master Files.
    - 1st and 2nd Sessions, A-C (6 folders)
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 128)
  - Master Files.
    - 1st and 2nd Sessions, D-Mc (20 folders)
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 129)
  - Master Files.
    - 1st and 2nd Session, M-Z (25 folders)
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 130)
  - Political Files, 1955-1966.
    - A, B (2 folders)
    - Campaign Material
    - Campaign, 1960
    - C
    - Democratic Committee--1st District Lists
    - D
    - E, F (2 folders)
    - General Election, 1962
    - General Political
    - Godwin, Mills--Campaign for Governor, 1965
    - Gubernatorial Campaign--Virginia, Primary, 11 July 1961
    - G
    - House of Delegates
    - H-K [I omitted] (3 folders)
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 131)
  - Political Files, 1955-1966.
    - May, Richard A.
    - M
    - Organizational Luncheon, September 1960
    - Q
    - Redistricting
    - R
    - Sample Letter--November Campaign, 1960
    - Senate Race, 1966--Harry Flood Byrd
    - Senate Race, 1966--Thomas Nelms Downing
    - Senate Race, 1966--A. Willis Robertson
    - Senate Race, 1966--Newspaper Clippings
    - State Appointments
    - State Senator
    - S
    - Testimonial Dinner, Chamberlin Hotel, 13 June 1964
    - T
    - Virginia and National Politics--Clippings
    - Veterans Organizations--1960 Campaign
- 89th Congress, 1965-1966. (Box 132)
  - Political Files, 1955-1966.
    - Voting Information
    - V
    - Women, 1960 Campaign
    - W
    - Young Democrats of Virginia
  - Voting Record.
    - 1st and 2nd Sessions (2 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 132)
  - [Military] Academies.
    Note: Military Academy files contain student academic information; they are therefore restricted due to Privacy Act considerations and may not be served.
    - U.S. Air Force Academy, 1967-1968 (2 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 133)
  - [Military] Academies.
    - U.S. Merchant Marine Academy, 1967-1968 (2 folders)
    - U.S. Military Academy, 1967-1968 (2 folders)
    - U.S. Naval Academy, 1967-1968 (3 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 134)
  - [Military] Academies.
    - U.S. Naval Academy, 1968 (1 folder)
    - Academies--General
    - Academy Appointees--(Graduating) Class of 1967 (2 folders)
    - Academy Appointees--(Graduating) Class of 1968
    - Out-of-District Applicants
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 135)
  - [Military] Academies.
    - Preparatory Schools
    - Withdrawn Nominees' File
    - Civil Service Examination for Applicants
    - Sample Letter--Academic
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Agriculture Committee (2 folders)
    - Agriculture Committee--Cherry Marketing Bill (H.R. 4282)
    - Agriculture Committee--Pear Marketing Order Bill (H.R. 10564)
    - 90th Yearbook of Agriculture
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 136)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Appropriations Committee
    - Appropriations Committee--Impacted Aid
    - Appropriations Committee--Impacted Aid Funds (P.L. 81-874)
    - Appropriations Committee--Neighborhood Youth Corps
    - Appropriations Committee--Ship Construction Abroad (H.R. 10738)
    - Armed Services Committee
    - Armed Services Committee--ABM Missile System--Safeguard
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 137)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Banking and Currency Committee (2 folders)
    - Banking and Currency Committee--Truth in Lending (H.R. 11601)
    - Commerce Committee
    - Crime Commission--Legislation
    - District of Columbia Committee
    - Education and Labor Committee (2 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 138)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Education and Labor Committee (2 folders)
    - Education and Labor Committee--Economic Opportunity Amendment
    - Education and Labor Committee--Collective Bargaining Rights (H.R. 4769, H.R. 16014)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 139)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Education and Labor Committee--Situs Picketing
    - Joint Economic Committee
    - Ethics Committee
    - Foreign Affairs Committee
    - Foreign Affairs Committee--Foreign Aid
    - General Legislation (2 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 140)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - General Legislation (4 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 141)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Government Operations
    - Government Operations--Contracting Out
    - House Administrative Committee
    - Humane Treatment of Animals
    - Interior and Insular Affairs
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce (3 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 142)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Fish Products Act of 1968
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--SEC Recommendation on Mutual Funds (H.R. 9510)
    - Joint Committee on Atomic Energy
    - Joint Committee on Printing
    - Judiciary Committee (4 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 143)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Judiciary Committee--Firearms [Gun Control] (7 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 144)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Judiciary Committee--Gun Control (4 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 145)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Judiciary Committee--Gun Control (1 folder)
    - Judiciary Committee--Open Housing (5 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 146)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Judiciary Committee--Open Housing (3 folders)
    - Judiciary Committee--Prayer Amendment (S.J. Res 148)
    - Judiciary Committee--Supreme Court Justices
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries.
      Note: Merchant Marine and Fisheries legislation has been microfilmed; see list in folder.
    - Post Office and Civil Service (2 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 147)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Post Office and Civil Service (1 folder)
    - Post Office and Civil Service--Legislation to Exempt PO from P.L. 90-364
    - Post Office and Civil Service--Retirement Bill (H.R. 770, 9825)
    - Public Works Committee
    - Public Works Committee--Standards for Truck Weight (S. 2658)
    - Public Works Committee--Beautification
    - Public Works Committee--Water Pollution
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 148)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Rules Committee
    - Select Committee on Small Business
    - Space Committee (3 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 149)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Space Committee (2 folders)
    - Space Committee--Space and Astronautics--Larry Bryant--UFOs
    - Committee on Official Standards of Conduct
    - Un-American Activities Committee
    - Veteran Affairs Committee
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 150)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Ways and Means Committee (2 folders)
    - Ways and Means Committee--European Travel Ban--Tax
    - Ways and Means Committee--Social Security Increase
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 151)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Ways and Means Committee--Surtax (2 folders)
  - General Files.
    - Accomack County
    - Accomplishments (2 folders)
    - Department of Agriculture--General (1 folder)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 152)
  - General Files.
    - Department of Agriculture--General (1 folder)
    - Department of Agriculture--Potatoes
    - Aid for International Development
    - Air Force
    - Air Pollution
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board
    - American Legion
    - Appointments
    - Armories
    - Army
    - U.S. Army Recruiting Command
    - Department of the Army--Activate Reservists
    - Army Reserve, 3rd Howitzer Battalion
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 153)
  - General Files.
    - Atkinson, Harry v. City of Newport News
    - Atomic Energy Commission [AEC]
    - A--General
    - Bateman, Herbert H.
    - Bellamy Award--Margarette S. Miller
    - Belle Haven
    - Bird, Collins
    - Bureau of the Budget
    - Byrd, Harry F., Jr.
    - B--General
    - Calling Cards--Personal
    - Capitol Calendar Requests
    - Cape Charles
    - Cape Hatteras
    - Cape Henry
    - Camp Perry
    - Cedar Hall
    - Cedar Island
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 154)
  - General Files.
    - Census(2 folders)
    - Chamber of Commerce
    - Chamberlin Hotel
    - Charles City County
    - Navigational Charts
    - Cheatham Annex
    - Chesapeake Bay Bridge Tunnel
    - Chincoteague--General
    - Chincoteague--Pony Penning
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 155)
  - General Files.
    - Christopher Newport College
    - Civil Aeronautics Board [CAB]
    - Civil Defense
    - Civil Service Commission [CSC]
    - Coast Guard--General
    - Coast Guard--Assateague Lighthouse
    - College Admissions
    - Colonial National Historical Park
    - Commemorative Stamps
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 156)
  - General Files.
    - Commerce Department--General
    - Commerce Department--Economic Census--Lewis H. Hall
    - Committee Assignments
    - Community Concert Association
    - Congratulations
    - Congressional Directory, 90th Congress
    - Customs--General
    - Customs--Customs Office Transfer
    - C--General
    - Department of Defense (1 folder)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 157)
  - General Files.
    - Department of Defense (1 folder)
    - Defense Language Institute
    - Delmarva
    - Democratic Caucus
    - District Office and Tours (2 folders)
    - Dulles Airport
    - D--General
    - Eastern Shore
    - General Employment and Position
    - Leif Ericson Day, 1967
    - USS Enterprise Painting at Mariners Museum
    - ESSO
    - Exhibits and Tours
    - Exmore, Town of
    - Expo
    - E--General
    - Farmers Home Administration [FHA]
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 158)
  - General Files.
    - Federal Aviation Administration [FAA] (2 folders)
    - Federal Communications Commission [FCC]
    - Federal Housing Authority--General
    - Federal Housing Authority--Mortgage Servicing--VA
    - Federal Power Commission [FPC]
    - Federal Trade Commission [FTC]
    - First District--General
    - First District--Budget, FY 1969
    - Fisherman Island
    - Flowers
    - Football Tickets
    - Forbes Candy
    - Fort Eustis--General
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 159)
  - General Files.
    - Fort Eustis--Biggs Air Force Base
    - Fort Eustis--RIF of Personnel on M/S Sagitta
    - Fort Monroe
    - Fort Story
    - Frederick College
    - F--General
    - Gallery Passes
    - General Assembly
    - General Services Administration [GSA]
    - Geneva Conference
    - Gifts--Personal
    - Given--Money for Gifts by TND
    - Gloucester
    - Grandis, Nancy
    - G--General
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 160)
  - General Files.
    - Hampton, City of
    - Hampton--Office Appointments
    - Hampton--City Schools
    - Hampton Institute
    - Hampton Roads Army Terminal
    - Hampton Roads Maritime Association
    - Hampton Roads Sanitation District Commission
    - Harrison Lake National Fish Hatchery
    - Hemisfair
    - Health, Education, and Welfare [HEW]--General (1 folder)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 161)
  - General Files.
    - Health, Education, and Welfare--General (1 folder)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare--National Teacher Corps
    - Health, Education, and Welfare--Rat Control--Floyd Thomas
    - Highway Department--General
    - Highway Department--Gaspar Morrell--Virginia Access Road
    - Highway Department--Three Sisters Bridge
    - Hill Burton Hospital Funds
    - Hog Island
    - Hollins Panel
    - House of Representatives--Opening Prayers, etc.
    - Housing
    - Housing and Urban Development [HUD]
    - H--General
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 162)
  - General Files.
    - Immigration
    - Internal Revenue Service [IRS]
    - Department of Interior
    - Interstate Commerce Commission [ICC]
    - I--General
    - Jamestown
    - Soviet Jewry
    - Johnson, Lyndon B.
    - Justice Department
    - J--General
    - Kecoughtan--General
    - Kecoughtan--VA Center (3 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 163)
  - General Files.
    - Kings' Point Merchant Marine Academy--General
    - Kings' Point Merchant Marine Academy--Board of Visitors--Meeting, 2 June 1967
    - Korean Incident--USS Pueblo
    - K--General
    - Labor Department
    - Langley Air Force Base--General
    - Langley Air Force Base--Thank You Letters
    - Library of Congress
    - Little Creek Amphibious Base
    - L--General
    - Marine Corps
    - Maring Engineers' Beneficial Association [MEBA] Training School
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 164)
  - General Files.
    - Marine Resources Commission--Dr. Hargis
    - Maritime Administration [MARAD]
    - Marshall, Clarence G.
    - Mathews County
    - Mid-East Crisis
    - Middlesex County
    - Monitor-Merrimack Memorial
    - M--General
    - NASA--General
    - NASA--Langley (Hampton)--Budget
    - NASA--Oyster Point Cyclotron, 1967 (1 folder)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 165)
  - General Files.
    - NASA--Oyster Point Cyclotron, 1967 (1 folder)
    - NASA--Wallops Island
    - National Guard
    - National Park Service
    - National Science Board
    - National Science Foundation--Drs. Mason and Swindler
    - Naval Air Rework Facility, Norfolk--Truman N. Holland
    - Naval Air Station Oceana
    - Naval Shipyards
    - Naval Weapons Station
    - Navy
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 166)
  - General Files.
    - Navy/Aeronautical Examiners
    - Newport News, City of--General (2 folders)
    - Newport News, City of--Economic Opportunity Committee
    - Newport News, City of--City Schools--HEW Decision
    - Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company--General
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 167)
  - General Files.
    - Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company--Hydraulic Turbines
    - Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company--Strike, July 1967
    - Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company--Tenneco Proxy Statement, 1968
    - Newsletters
    - Newspapers
    - Nice letters
    - Norfolk, City of
    - Norfolk Marine Hospital
    - Norfolk Naval Shipyard
    - Northampton County
    - N--General
    - Oceanography Institute
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 168)
  - General Files.
    - Office of Economic Opportunity [OEO] (2 folders)
    - Office Help
    - Office Memos
    - Old Dominion College--General
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 169)
  - General Files.
    - Old Dominion College--Peace Essay
    - Onancock
    - O--General
    - Pacific Far East--Guam Route
    - Page School
    - Parkinson's Disease
    - Passes for TND's Office Staff
    - Patrick Henry Airport
    - Patrick Henry Boys Plantation
    - Patronage
    - Peace Corps
    - Peninsula Arena-Auditorium Authority
    - Peninsula Chamber of Commerce
    - Peninsula Ports Authority
    - Peninsula Shipbuilders Association
    - Photographs (2 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 170)
  - General Files.
    - Photographs (1 folder)
    - Poquoson--General
    - Poquoson--Sewage
    - Port of Hampton Roads
    - Post Office Department (2 folders).
      Note: These Post Office folders contain graphic pornographic advertisements which were bulk mailed to Mr. Downing's constituents, and subsequently to him.
    - Powell, Adam Clayton
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 171)
  - General Files.
    - Publications--General (2 folders)
    - Publications--Congressional Record
    - P, Q--General (2 folders)
    - Research--General--T. Hutton
    - Riots (1 folder)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 172)
  - General Files.
    - Riots (1 folder)
    - Riverside Hospital--Peninsula Mental Health Center
    - Rural Electrification in Virginia
    - R--General
    - Saluda
    - Saxis
    - Seafood Marketing Development Program--Overseas--Gen. Tunner
    - Selective Service
    - Sewers
    - New Shipyard
    - Small Business Administration [SBA]
    - Social Security [HEW]
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 173)
  - General Files.
    - Southeastern Electric
    - Spong, William
    - Department of State--General (2 folders)
    - Department of State--Aid to International Development [AID]
    - Sudeten German Day on Whitsuntide--Dr. Becher
    - Summer Employment (1 folder)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 174)
  - General Files.
    - Summer Employment (1 folder)
    - Supreme Court
    - Surplus Property
    - Sympathy
    - S--General
    - Tangier
    - Tariffs
    - Thiessen, Wayne
    - Torrey Canyon IMCO Conference
    - Tours
    - Department of Transportation
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 175)
  - General Files.
    - Treasury Department
    - Tuck, Bill
    - T--General
    - United Nations
    - U--General
    - Veterans Administration [VA]
    - Viet Nam (2 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 176)
  - General Files.
    - Viet Nam (2 folders)
    - Virginia Bar Association
    - Virginia Beach, City of
    - Virginia Beach District Office--General
    - Virginia Beach District Office--Furniture
    - Virginia Beach District Office--Mass Transportation
    - Virginia Council on Health and Medical Care
    - Virginia Electric Power Company
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 177)
  - General Files.
    - Virginia Institute of Marine Science [VIMS]
    - Virginia Military Institute [VMI]
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute [VPI]
    - Virginia State College [VSC]
    - Virginia State Ports Authority
    - Commonwealth of Virginia--General (2 folders)
    - University of Virginia
    - V--General
    - Wachapreague
    - Wedgewood Dinner Theater
    - Democratic Whip
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 178)
  - General Files.
    - White House--General
    - White House--Tours
    - Whittaker Memorial Hospital, Newport News
    - College of William and Mary
    - Williamsburg, City of
    - Wise Point--Surplus Property
    - W--General
    - York County
    - Yorktown
    - Zucker, Sylvia--Peninsula Association for Retarded Children
    - Zucker, Sylvia--Multiple Disability Diagnostic and Treatment Facility
    - X-Z--General
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 179)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, January-September 1967 (9 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 180)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, October-December 1967 (4 folders)
    - Invitations Regretted, January-April 1967 (4 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 181)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Regretted, May-December 1967 (8 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 182)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Extended, 1967
    - Day-at-a-Glance, Daybook, 1967
    - Invitations Accepted, January-April 1968 6 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 183)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, May-December 1968 (9 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 184)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Regretted, January-June 1968 (6 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 185)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Regretted, July-December 1968 (6 folders)
    - Invitations Extended, 1968
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 186)
  - Legislation Enacted.
    - Blow Property in Yorktown--Colonial National Historical Park (P.L. 90-74)
    - Gallant, J. Edward (H.J. Res. 1268)
    - Gibson, Henry (P.L. 90-305)
    - Rusk, LT Willard Herndon--Relief (P.L. 90-276)
    - Watson, Waverly, Jr. (H.R. 8091)
  - Legislation Not Enacted, 1st Session.
    - Dr. Alper--Dentist Licensing (H.R. 3973)
    - Animal Drug Amendments to the Federal Food, Drug and Cosmetic Act, (H.R. 7165)
    - Anti-Riot Legislation (H.R. 421)
    - Castaneda, Dr. David de Jesus--Relief (H.R. 4539)
    - Dairy Import Act of 1967 (H.R. 10295)
    - Fair Labor Standards Amendments of 1966--Migratory Workers
    - Farm Minimum Wage (H.R. 4348)
    - Federal Flood Insurance (H.R. 4225)
    - Haghichi, Sassanvash (H.R. 9075)
    - Hampton Hardwood Corporation (H.R. 4375)
    - Hernandez, Alberto M.--Immigration (H.R. 12245)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 187)
  - Legislation Not Enacted, 1st Session.
    - Humane Treatment of Animals (H.R. 13617)
    - Internal Security Act of 1950--Amendment (H.R. 12601)
    - Juror Travel Expenses (H.R. 7975)
    - Kaiulani--Loan for Restoration and Return (H. J. Res. 751)
    - Langley Research Center--50th Anniversary (H. J. Res. 799)
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries.
    - Medicare--Prescription Drugs (H.R. 6363)
    - Migratory Bird Treaty Act (H.R. 14310)
    - Ng Shu Kan [Eugene Eng]--Relief (H.R. 8089)
    - Orphanidys, George A. [Peter Vamvouklis] (H.R. 8090)
    - Panama Canal--Retain (H. Con Res. 399)
    - Pedroso, Dr. Frank--Relief (H.R. 4540)
    - Premium Pay--OAST (H.R. 7976)
    - Select Committee on Standards of Conduct
    - Textile Imports (H.R. 6220)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 188)
  - Legislation Not Enacted, 1st Session.
    - Trading with Communist Countries (H. Res. 847)
    - Tudela, Dr. Francisco Guillermo--Relief (H.R. 4541)
    - Vesting Title to the Ocean Floor in the U.N. (H. J. Res. 818)
  - Legislation Not Enacted, 2nd Session.
    - Camping on Public Land (H. J. Res. 1256)
    - Extend Commercial Fisheries Research and Development Act of 1964 (H.R. 18809)
    - Obligating France to Repay Debt (H. Con. Res. 659)